[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "In what year was Sega Genesis released in North America?",
        "options": [
            "1989",
            "1999",
            "1975",
            "1991"
        ],
        "answer": "1989"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following video games takes place in a dystopian underwater city called Rapture ?",
        "options": [
            "Bioshock",
            "Half - Life",
            "God Of War",
            "Fallout 3"
        ],
        "answer": "Bioshock"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What Nintendo system was released after the N64 and before the Wii ?",
        "options": [
            "Gamecube",
            "Nintendo",
            "Virtual Boy",
            "Super Nintendo"
        ],
        "answer": "Gamecube"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Honda, Dhalsim and Chun Li are all characters from what video game series ?",
        "options": [
            "Street Fighter",
            "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",
            "Battletoads",
            "Mortal Kombat"
        ],
        "answer": "Street Fighter"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What color is the ring of death on an XBOX that signifies a hardware failure ?",
        "options": [
            "Red",
            "Blue",
            "Yellow",
            "Green"
        ],
        "answer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What classic beat - 'em-up game featured brothers Billy Lee and Jimmy (also nicknamed Spike and Hammer)?",
        "options": [
            "Double Dragon",
            "Smash Brothers",
            "Ninja Gaiden",
            "Snow Brothers"
        ],
        "answer": "Double Dragon"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What classic beat - 'em-up game featured brothers Billy Lee and Jimmy (also nicknamed Spike and Hammer)?",
        "options": [
            "Double Dragon",
            "Smash Brothers",
            "Ninja Gaiden",
            "Snow Brothers"
        ],
        "answer": "Double Dragon"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How many bits was the Super Nintendo Entertainment System?",
        "options": [
            "16",
            "8",
            "128",
            "64"
        ],
        "answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What character do you play as in The Legend Of Zelda ?",
        "options": [
            "Link",
            "Gandolf",
            "Chimmy",
            "Peter"
        ],
        "answer": "Link"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What 64 - bit Sega system was a predecessor to the PlayStation and Nintendo 64 ?",
        "options": [
            "Saturn",
            "Dreamcast",
            "Commodore 128",
            "3DO"
        ],
        "answer": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "The game Grand Theft Auto was released primarily for what gaming system ?",
        "options": [
            "PlayStation",
            "Dreamcast",
            "XBOX",
            "NES"
        ],
        "answer": "PlayStation"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which James Bond film was made into a game for the Nintendo 64 console and later for the Wii console ?",
        "options": [
            "Goldeneye",
            "Thunderball",
            "Moonraker",
            "Goldfinger"
        ],
        "answer": "Goldeneye"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Which popular video game features an ex - Special Forces operator named Jack Carver, who is stranded in Micronesia ?",
        "options": [
            "Far Cry",
            "Halo 2",
            "Left 4 Dead",
            "Max Payne"
        ],
        "answer": "Far Cry"
    }
]